[
    {
        "front": "うれます||\n［パンが～］ ",
        "back": "[bread] sell, be sold",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "おどります|",
        "back": "dance",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "かみます|",
        "back": "chew, bite",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "えらびます| ",
        "back": "choose",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "かよいます|\n［だいがくに～］ ",
        "back": "go to and from [university]",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "メモします||| ",
        "back": "take a memo",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "まじめ［な］ ",
        "back": "serious",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "ねっしん［な］",
        "back": "earnest",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "えらい ",
        "back": "great, admirable",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "ちょうど いい",
        "back": "proper, just right",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "けしき",
        "back": "scenery, view",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "びよういん",
        "back": "hair solon",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "だいどころ",
        "back": "kitchen",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "けいけん ",
        "back": "experience (～が あります: be experienced, ～を します: experience)",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "ちから ",
        "back": "power",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "にんき",
        "back": "popularity ([がくせいに] ～が あります: be popular [with students])",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "かたち ",
        "back": "form, shape",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "いろ ",
        "back": "colour",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "あじ ",
        "back": "taste",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "ガム ",
        "back": "chewing gum",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "しなもの ",
        "back": "goods",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "ねだん ",
        "back": "price",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうりょう ",
        "back": "salary",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "ボーナス ",
        "back": "bonus",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "ゲーム",
        "back": "(computer) game",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "ばんぐみ ",
        "back": "programme",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "ドラマ ",
        "back": "drama",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "かしゅ",
        "back": "singer",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうせつ ",
        "back": "novel",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうせつか",
        "back": "novelist",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "～か",
        "back": " -er, -ist, etc. (e.g. painter, novelist)",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "～き",
        "back": "~ machine",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "むすこ ",
        "back": "(my) son ",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "むすこさん* ",
        "back": "(someone else's) son ",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "むすめ ",
        "back": "(my) daughter ",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "むすめさん*",
        "back": "(someone else's) daughter ",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "じぶん",
        "back": "oneself",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうらい ",
        "back": "future",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "しばらく ",
        "back": "a little while",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "たいてい ",
        "back": "usually, mostly",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "それに ",
        "back": "in addition",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "それで ",
        "back": "and so",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "［ちょっと］おねがい が あるんですが。",
        "back": "I have a [small] favour to ask",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "じつは",
        "back": "as a matter of fact",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "かいわ",
        "back": "conversation",
        "chapter": 28
    },
    {
        "front": "うーん",
        "back": "well, let me see, hmm…",
        "chapter": 28
    }
]